<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="type_description_aqua">Working out in water is an effective way to activate the whole body, as the intensity and toughness is directly connected to the size, power and frequency of the movements you choose to work with. That\'s is the main reason as for why this class becomes just as tough as you\'d like for it to be. This class has you standing on the bottom of the pool to improve your cardio, strength and mobility by using your own body weight (or at times, certain equipment), accompanied by motivating music.</string>
    <string name="type_description_aqua_balte">Working out in water is an effective way to activate the whole body, as the intensity and toughness is directly connected to the size, power and frequency of the movements you choose to work with. That\'s is the main reason as for why this class becomes just as tough as you\'d like for it to be. This class has you hovering in the deeper end of the pool to improve your cardio, strength and mobility by using your own body weight (or at times, certain equipment), accompanied by motivating music. An added benefit from not being able to stand at the bottom is that you really have to activate your core to keep yourself afloat.</string>
    <string name="type_description_aqua_box">Aqua Box is a workout that gets its inspiration from various martial arts, using kicks and punches to improve both your cardio and your strength. Suitable for everyone.</string>
    <string name="type_description_aqua_tt">The ultimate strength, cardio and mobility workout in water - really intense with simple exercises. The class is divided in various parts where you cycle hard work and recovery. The warmup consists of a few simple movements, and the main exercises increase the intensity per repetition. All in all it\'s a class where we work on our cardio, strength and mobility accompanied by motivating music.</string>
    <string name="type_description_barre">The main source of inspiration for this class was a mixture of balet, functional fitness and yoga. You\'ll work your way through your whole body in an effective (yet lenient) fashion, focusing on strength, body control, core stability, mobility and balance. No previous balet or yoga experience is needed as the exercies are based on entry-level techniques. Barre Move is a concept developed by Maria Olofsson and Åsa Fornander.</string>
    <string name="type_description_basketball">On our basketball sessions you can play against others in mixed teams. The participants are split up in teams at the session itself, and the level of skill usually varies - everyone is welcome to join in by reserving a spot on our website/app. Play together and have fun!</string>
    <string name="type_description_beach">Beach volleyball is usually played in teams of two, but can easily be extended for more participants. When you reserve a field you\'ll need to bring a ball, friends and foes. There are four fields in Las Palmas, all of them available for reservationId via our website/app.</string>
    <string name="type_description_bodybalance">The class suits most people and consists of a set of exercises with roots in yoga, tai chi and pilates. A typical BODYBALANCE® class revolves around using your own body as equipment, with focus on breathing and presence. A new choreography is released every three months in typical Les Mills fashion.</string>
    <string name="type_description_bodycombat">BODYCOMBAT® is a cardio-oriented workout that\'s inspired by various martial arts including karate, taekwondo, capoeira, boxing and muay thai. It\'s a fast paced class with lots of power and energi where you use punches and kicks to work on your cardio, strength and coordination. Anyone can participate, although a certain level of fitness would be beneficial due to the sometimes high pace.</string>
    <string name="type_description_bodyjam">BODYJAM® fits anyone that loves to dance and wants to combine it with coordination and cardio. The choreography is a bit challenging and combines a lot of different styles like house, hiphop, latino and reggae dancehall. You\'ll most certainly have improved your control of your own body after a few classes.</string>
    <string name="type_description_bodypump">BODYPUMP® improves your strength using barbells, weights and your own body as your tools. It suits pretty much everyone as you\'re in control over how much weight you\'re using. The class itself offers you a challenging and balanced full body workout, as well as motivating music and an uplifting group dynamic.</string>
    <string name="type_description_bodystep">BODYSTEP® is a choreographed step class from Les Mills where the focus is on energy, power and happiness. Simple yet challenging step combinations make you work at a high and intensive pace. The music is chirpy, energy packed and singalong friendly, and helps you get even more out of the various combinations. This class is perfect for anyone that wants to dance their way to better cardio, coordination and strength.</string>
    <string name="type_description_bodyvive">BODYVIVE® is a form of training with motivating and singalong friendly music, making you happy and full of new energy. The workout itself strengthens your body, bumps up your cardio and improves both your mobility and balance. Every class is built with simple step combinations and lots of time to feel the rythm your body and in the music. The strength oriented parts of the class utilizes a rubberband and your own bodyweight.</string>
    <string name="type_description_cardio_training">Cardio Training is an intense circuit training class that you can adapt and customize around your training experience. You set your own pace and thus also create your own challenge!</string>
    <string name="type_description_cirkeltraning">Every Circuit Training class consists of ten strength exercises combined with cardio on a bike/crosstraininer. No confusing settings are needed, as you only need to set the weight and pick a number of repetitions to do. Work hard for 40 seconds and rest for 20 while switching stations - a lamp in the ceiling will let you know when it\'s time. One lap around the stations takes 16 minutes, and our recommendation is that you do 1-3 laps per occasion.</string>
    <string name="type_description_core_control">Core Control from Motivation and Move, is a pre-choreographed and efficient class, where you work on stability and balance. Exercises are based on the body\'s core and build up strength and mobility for the entire body. During the class you work at intervals at your own pace and based on your own level. This training will help you to use your body effectively, whether you want a wonderful Sunday walk or compete at the elite level. The class can be combined with other group training.</string>
    <string name="type_description_cxworx">CXWORX® is a heavier form of exercise where you use both rubber bands, weights and your own body weight as a tool. It is a pre-choreographed program from Les Mills, which challenges you to improve your level of exercise while strengthening your body. CXWORX® focuses on the muscles of the trunk and the muscles that bind the upper body and lower body. You challenge yourself both mentally and physically as well as improve your body control and balance. It includes both landscape and standing exercises. You decide how intensive you want it to be.</string>
    <string name="type_description_cykel">Our Cykel classes contain a variety of straight stretches and slopes at different pace and often feature intervals. Tough challenges are mixed with lighter segments to make you enjoy and sweat at the same time. By activating large muscle groups, Cykel provides a good fitness training. The instructor sets up his class and is always there to guide, motivate and challenge you - allowing variation in both music and layout. Combine Cykel with any of our other group training classes, such as CXWORX®, Core Control or BODYPUMP®.</string>
    <string name="type_description_cykel_ftp_testpass">On our Cykel Watt classes, you train in different wattzones based on your own functional threshold. The threshold value is called Functional Treshold Power and is the maximum watt value you could hold for one hour. You get it by going to one of our FTP test passes. The threshold value helps you train in the correct zone under our Cykel Watt pass. If you have not previously calculated your threshold value, you can enter gender, weight and how much you work per week, then the bicycle estimates a general value. However, the best and safest value is always available by visiting one of our FTP test passes. If you need help with the settings on the bike, talk to the instructor. Note that your leg length may affect the ability to get a good setting.</string>
    <string name="type_description_cykel_watt">Our heart rate may vary on a daily basis but the watts are always constant. By starting with Cykel Watt, you can keep track of your development in a measurable and fun way over time. Our instructors decide on their arrangements in terms of intervals and pace, and they keep the same schedule for at least six weeks to enable you to see your progress over time. During the class you can track exactly which zone you are in, both by looking at numbers, but also by following the color of the display. The colors make it clear for you to see if you are training in the correct zone based on your threshold, and they also help in creating a lovely atmosphere in the room - it even makes it easier for the instructor to guide you through the class!</string>
    <string name="type_description_dance">Dance is a fun form of fitness training that includes dance-inspired step combinations. We train both fitness, agility and mobility backed by motivating music, and both jumps and spins may occur and the tempo may be quite high. The choreography is built methodically, step by step and is set-up in different ways to make it easier to follow along.</string>
    <string name="type_description_dance_fusion">Dance Fusion is a dance class that looks different from time to time. Under each class we focus on a special theme or a special dance style. You will be able to dance different dance styles, train cardio and coordination, and challenge yourself to be here and now. It\'s a dance class where you have to let go of the barriers and just have fun during your workout. The dance styles you will be testing on include lyrical jazz, broadway jazz, oriental dance, house and hip-hop.</string>
    <string name="type_description_familjegympa">Train your child\'s motor skills and agility! The aim of familegympa is that the children should feel safe, belonging and have a positive experience of movement and activity. This creates motivation and continued interest in keeping themselves active. Music, text and movement create a whole that is easy for the children to understand. We keep the presence, joy and energy high by varying different themes during the class. You and your child get to hang out and interact creatively and will definitely have a fun and fast-paced experience together!</string>
    <string name="type_description_familjesim">During familjesim the depths of Bottenviken are adjusted to suit children. You as a parent are responsible for your children when you are swimming together . Other times, the Bottenviken pool is intended for workouts with or without an instructor. Familjesim is free for anyone with a valid IKSU card with access to IKSU sports - you only pay for your children.</string>
    <string name="type_description_fotboll">Indoor soccer is fast decision and close combat all the time. Who does the most goals and who defends himself best? Book a football pass and play with others in mixed teams. The passport has no leader, the participants divide themselves into teams. Simply book a place in the class via our booking web or booking application. Play together, mostly because it\'s fun.</string>
    <string name="type_description_fysgympa">Fysgympa 80 is our classic! The class provides versatile and functional workout for the entire body where you exercise, fitness and mobility, both with and without tools, are effective and fun. Through the music you are inspired to movement and exercise pleasure with good effect. The pass is led by an instructor who constantly peeps. All fitness packages include warming, stretching, fitness, strength, running, downhill, relaxation and stretching. The conditional parts contain running and jumping but you can always choose another option. The tools used are dumbbells, weights, bars, balls, boards, carpets and rubber bands. The physiotherapist also includes interval-based stationary training and always ends with rusher for a real accomplisher!</string>
    <string name="type_description_grit_strength">Les Mills GRIT ™ is 30 minutes high intensity interval training. GRIT ™ strength focuses on strength and we use a bar and weight plate. Effective exercise that improves your oxygen uptake, strength and stamina. We recommend some training habits.</string>
    <string name="type_description_gympa">Gympa suits everyone regardless of previous experience. The class provides versatile and functional workout for the entire body where you exercise, fitness and mobility, both with and without tools, are effective and fun. Through the music you are inspired to movement and exercise pleasure with good effect. The pass is led by an instructor who constantly peaks you as a participant. All fitness packages include warming, stretching, fitness, strength, running, downhill, relaxation and stretching. Gympan\'s fitness parts contain elements of running and jumping, but you can always choose another option. The tools used are dumbbells, weights, bars, balls, boards, carpets and rubber bands.</string>
    <string name="type_description_indoor_walking">The training form may be similar to cycling but you use a form of crosstrainer, a so-called walker. Our Indoor Walking pass includes a variety of straight stretches and backs at different pace and often feature intervals. Load, position and tempo are varied during the course of the class. This way the class becomes as tough or easy as you want. By engaging in large muscle groups, Indoor Walking gives a good fitness effect. Indoor Walking is not only good for fitness but also for our balance, stability and bonfire strength. The instructor sets up his class and is always there to guide, peep and challenge you. This creates variation in both music and layout. Combine Indoor Walking with any of our other group training classes, such as CXWORX®, Core Control or BODYPUMP®. Through that you get a big challenge for the whole body!</string>
    <string name="type_description_innebandy">Do you want to play Sweden\'s most common indoor sports with others? Book yourself on a session in our schedule and play in a mixed team every time. The class has no leader, the participants divide themselves into teams. Simply book a place on the class via our booking web or booking application.</string>
    <string name="type_description_intensivgympa">Intensivgympa suits you who want higher intensity. The class provides versatile and functional workout for the entire body where you exercise, fitness and mobility, both with and without tools, are effective and fun. Through the music you are inspired to exercise and exercise pleasure with good exercise effect. The pass is led by an instructor who constantly peaks you as a participant. All our fitness packages include warming, stretching, fitness, strength, running, downhill, relaxation and stretching. The passport\'s fitness parts contain running and jumping but you can always choose another option. The constituents contain torque with and without tools. The tools used are dumbbells, weights, bars, balls, boards, carpets and rubber bands.</string>
    <string name="type_description_jarngympa">Järngympa is an intensive gymnastics gym with dynamic steps and powerful movements that suits you with some exercise difficulties or want to progress on Intensivgympa. Our gym is versatile and functional exercise for the entire body where you exercise, fitness and mobility, both with and without tools, are efficient and fun. The passport contains elements of stationary training. The passport\'s fitness parts contain running and jumping but you can always choose another option. The tools used are dumbbells, weights, bars, balls, boards, carpets and rubber bands.</string>
    <string name="type_description_klattring">You\'ll find two climbing walls at IKSU sport. In the stadium of the Helsinki stadium you will find a 400 m² climbing wall, and in the entrance hall there is a newly built climbing wall of about 60 m². The climbing wall is also a place to work out, meet people, exchange tips and ideas and hang out with friends. The walls are maintained by our section IKSU climbing. The section also holds in Test-on-Pass and climbing courses such as the Green Card course. The climbing wall located above the stadium in the Helsinki stadium is open at the same time as IKSU sport. Note that the wall can be closed when different elite teams play their matches in Helsinki, as well as when any exams or fairs borrow the location.</string>
    <string name="type_description_les_mills_rpm">RPM® is a pre-choreographed class bike of Les Mills where you ride to the rhythm of powerful music in the hills, on the straights and up the mountain peaks in the time course and intervals. You challenge your stamina and strengthen your oxygenation. You choose yourself how intense you want it to be so the class also suits beginners. The instructor guides you through the terrain and helps you find the right feeling and peeps you to take some extra. You will notice that you become more persistent and stronger after a few times.</string>
    <string name="type_description_les_mills_sprint">LES MILLS SPRINT ™ is 30 minutes high intensity interval training with the bike as equipment. The class involves power, strength and speed. Exercise difficulty is an advantage. If you need help with the settings on the bike, talk to the instructor. Note that your leg length may affect the ability to get a good setting.</string>
    <string name="type_description_mamma_baby">Mom baby is a custom training for you who are new mom. We help you at your level and continue your training. Here you work on cardio, strength and mobility with the focus on the deep and stabilizing muscles. The instructor sets up his class and is always there to guide, peep and challenge you. This creates variation in both music and layout. During our mom-baby classes, the children and the social community are as important as the training. In addition to Mom Baby, we recommend the following classes in the first months after delivery: Indoor Walking, Bike, Pilates and Aqua.</string>
    <string name="type_description_mojo_flex">The class is simple, efficient and easily accessible. Can be trained directly after all types of physical classes or as an independent class. MOJO Flex® lets you recover the best between the tough workouts while charging the batteries to perform even better during the next physical challenge.</string>
    <string name="type_description_pilates">A calmer exercise style where you work on your stability, mobility and strength in predominantly deepening muscles around your core, the center of the body. Pilates suits everyone.</string>
    <string name="type_description_pilates_cirkel">Pilates is a gentle functional exercise that combines strength, mobility and coordination with focus on the bonfire, pelvic stabilization, and control of the abdominal muscles. You get a good posture, become strong and smooth throughout your body. Everyone can train Pilates - women, men, young, old, athletes and elite riders. The training form has also proved very suitable as rehab training for back and neck disorders. Many physiotherapists, chiropractors, naprapaths and doctors recommend Pilates.</string>
    <string name="type_description_pilates_reformer">Pilates is a gentle functional exercise that combines strength, mobility and coordination with focus on the bonfire, pelvic stabilization, and control of the abdominal muscles. When the body\'s all muscles interact in the best way, you can use the body efficiently and comfortably no matter what you do in everyday life. Training in Reforming Machine is also a good tool for those who want to build the body when rehabilitating various injuries. Pilates Reform suits everyone.</string>
    <string name="type_description_pilates_reformer_rehab">Pilates is a gentle exercise that focuses on body awareness. A combination of strength, mobility and coordination with focus on the bonfire, stabilization of the pelvis and control of the abdominal muscles provide a stronger body. Pilates has proven to be very suitable as rehab training for for example neck and back pain and the training method is recommended by many physiotherapists, chiropractors, naprapathies and doctors. Below the class there is the possibility of personal guidance and adaptation.</string>
    <string name="type_description_punchout">Strikes, kicks and technicians from different martial arts create an intensive training form where you work in pairs and in groups. Under the class, gloves and mitts are used in different sizes, and you can participate regardless of fitness level. The instructor makes sure everyone has someone to work out with. You will get sweaty, so do not forget the water bottle.</string>
    <string name="type_description_shbam">SH\'BAM® is both a fun and social way of exercising and a perfect opportunity to become a star on the dance floor. It is a preconfigured dance class from Les Mills for those who want to work out fitness, coordination and at the same time have fun in the meantime. The dance styles vary between the songs and the music is a mix of list sets played at clubs around the world, well-known classic and Latin American rhythms. The mood is permissive and there is no requirement for prior knowledge in dance or other coordinated forms of training.</string>
    <string name="type_description_soma_move">The whole class is an uninterrupted flow of different movement patterns where you both exercise strength, fitness, mobility, stability and balance. The stiff becomes looser and the good body control gets stronger.</string>
    <string name="type_description_squash">Sunday evenings between 20:00 and 21:30 with start 25/9 2016 there is the possibility to book and practice squash under the supervision and guidance of the section\'s skilled instructors. We have booked all four lanes and accommodate ten players - which guarantees a lot of playing time for each registered player. The class begins with a review and exercises. Then you play one set and then you change and play against someone else. It\'s a fun way to meet others who play squash and develop their game. On each class there is someone from the Squash section on site and gives instructions and tips. Balls and rackets are available for loan.</string>
    <string name="type_description_step">Fitness training on step box with different combinations of steps for inspirational music. Fits you who might have trained with a step box earlier. The level is slightly easier than StepDance, but still has some challenging step combinations. Effective and fun-filled exercise with step box as a starting point. Sometimes the instructor puts in a testimonial at the end of the class. Both weights and body weight are used as tools.</string>
    <string name="type_description_stepbas">No prerequisites in step are required. In a noiseless and permissive manner, the instructor guides you through the choreography. The choreography is based on simple basic steps, which are methodically and gradually taught. At the end of the class, all step combinations will be put together and you as a participant will be able to let go. Sometimes the instructor puts in a testimonial at the end of the class. Both weights and body weight are used as tools.</string>
    <string name="type_description_stepdance">Suitable for those who have trained a step earlier. The stage combinations are more advanced and inspired by different dance styles. The instructor guides you into a dance dance and challenging class. Both jumps and spins may occur and the tempo may be quite high. The choreography is built up step by step and methodically in various ways to make it easier to come along.</string>
    <string name="type_description_stepmuskel">Here you work on cardio, strength and coordination in a simple and efficient manner. Variable and simple step combinations combined with strength exercises. This allows you to exercise throughout the body. Under the strengths, weights and body weight are used as tools. Certain habits of step are to recommend, but no requirement.</string>
    <string name="type_description_total_training">The classes are divided into several stations and you do the exercises at your own pace. The exercises are performed with body weight, bars, medicine balls, kettlebells and other fun tools. We recommend that you as a participant have some training habits. If you have just started training, we recommend you try Pilates Circle, Fysgympa and Cardio Training.</string>
    <string name="type_description_total_training_buren">Functional training with a wide mix of fitness, strength, mobility, precision and coordination. The class is kept in the cage of Split (the gym\'s upstairs) on IKSU sport. It gives you the same high-intensity training as the other Total Training passes, but using the cage\'s various tools and positions in a limited space. We train very close to each other, which increases the experience a further snap.</string>
    <string name="type_description_total_training_ute">Here you get a wide mix of cardio, strength, mobility, precision and coordination. The classes are station-based and you do the exercises at your own pace. Exercises are performed with body weight, rocks, tires, branches and more. Weather and surfaces vary, creating even more variation in your training. We recommend some training habits.</string>
    <string name="type_description_volleyball">Suitable for those who like balls, jumping and fast footwork. The classes are mixed and have no leader, the participants divide themselves into teams. You can book the easiest place on your passport via our booking web or booking application. IKSU volleyball is our section of volleyball competition.</string>
    <string name="type_description_yoga">A low-intensity exercise form based on a flow of movements and breath with a focus on presence. The movements are derived from the physical yoga traditions and are performed entirely based on your prerequisites. Yoga helps you to well-being and harmony in both body and mind. The class ends with a relaxation. You do not need to be moving in your body to participate in Yoga.</string>
    <string name="type_description_yoga_latt">Easy Yoga helps you become strong, moving, present and harmonious. It is a low-intensity exercise that is based on a flow of motion and breath with a focus on presence. The movements are derived from the physical yoga traditions and are performed entirely based on your prerequisites. You do not need to be moving in the body to participate. The class ends with relaxation.</string>
    <string name="type_description_yoga_mindful">Mindful yoga strengthens the body and all its functions. Exercises are performed slowly with consciousness, relaxation and in association with breathing. It is based on the fact that, without performance, you explore the possibilities of your body without exceeding its limits. 45-minute physical exercises that then end with guided relaxation.</string>
    <string name="type_description_yoga_mindful_bas">Mindful Yoga base is based on the fact that, without performance, you explore your body\'s possibilities without exceeding its limits. The class will help you increase your presence and concentration. Mindful Yoga bass consists of 45 minutes of physical exercises which then end with 10 minutes of guided relaxation.</string>
    <string name="type_description_yoga_yin">Yinyoga is a yoga class with simple sitting and lying positions that focus on the deeper tissues of the body. You stay in the same position for several minutes while practicing conscious presence. All positions are based on you and your body\'s ability, so it does not matter how the position looks. Yinyoga increases your mobility, reduces tension in the body and helps you to find peace and harmony in a stressed and fast way of life. You do not need any previous experience of yoga.</string>
    <string name="type_description_zumba">Zumba® is a dance class with inspiration from Latin American dance styles, for those who like to dance and at the same time want to work out fitness. No previous knowledge required. Hot Latin American rhythms like Cumbia, Salsa, Samba and Merengue have been combined with delicious dance steps that exercise the entire body. The instructor guides you into the dance and you will be able to release the dance floor in a simple and permissive manner. It\'s so fun that you do not even think of exercising! The atmosphere is warm, happy and permissive.</string>
</resources>